Guide to the Dwight Hall, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Dwight Hall, Yale University, records
1881-2017
RU 47
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
111.75
The records consist of correspondence, minutes of meetings, financial records, membership lists, program records, committee records, scrapbooks, subject files, conference records, publications and printed material, and related materials concerning the activities of Dwight Hall at Yale.
Dwight Hall (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 39-B (YRG 39-B), Records documenting specific religious denominations or groups.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from Dwight Hall, 1988, 1994-1995, and 2018.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Biographical / Historical
Dwight Hall, a religious and service organization at Yale University, was originally founded as the Young Men's Christian Association at Yale in 1881.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, minutes of meetings, financial records, membership lists, program records, committee records, scrapbooks, subject files, conference records, publications and printed material, and related materials concerning the activities of Dwight Hall at Yale.
Church work; College students in missionary work; College students -- Religious life; Service learning; Universities and colleges -- Religion; Dwight Hall (Yale University); Yale University -- Religion; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Students; Young Men's Christian Association (Yale University)
- Records, 1881-1937; Accession 19ND-A-163
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - General Records of the Y.M.C.A.
    - Membership Lists and Dues
      - 1892-1893 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1893-1894 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1894-1898 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1899-1901 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Minutes
      - 1881-1894 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - 1894-1905 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - 1905-1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Policy Book by George Dahl, 1907-1908 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - President's Private Book, 1896-1911 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Reference Book -- "Dope Book" [guides, or memo books, for the running of the Y.M.C.A.]
      - 1907-1908 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - 1908-1909 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - 1910-1912 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Treasurer's Records
      - 1892-1897 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - 1892-1902 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 1898-1903 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - 1902-1910 (and 1 page from 1915-1916) (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - James Howard in Account with James Martin Fund, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Affiliated Christian Associations at Yale and Y.M.C.A. Committees
    - Graduate Committee minutes, 1885-1897 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Graduate Committee scrapbook, 1901-1904, 1915-1916 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Handbook Committee scrapbook and correspondence [see also Dwight Hall - Associated Record], 1894-1896 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Suggestions for Advertising Special Meetings by D. H. Leavens, 1908 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Systematic Giving Committee
      - 1894-1898 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - 1900-1903 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - University Council minutes, 1908-1910 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Groups and Meetings Sponsored by the Y.M.C.A.
    - Bible Study committee, Â 1897-1913 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Bible Study department, 1893-1898 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Christian Mission constitution, list of members, records, 1879-1892 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Christian Mission deacon's reportsÂ, 1891-1893 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Hope Mission
      - Duties of officers, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Register, 1893-1895 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Secretary's book, 1913-1917 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Jonathan Edwards Club secretary and treasurer's book, 1907-1916 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Prayer Meeting, 1886-1888 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Student Volunteer Band
      - Scrapbook, 1895-1898 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Record, 1904-1905 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Record book, 1905-1920 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Student Volunteers for Foreign Missions
      - Rules and members [Yale-in-China ?], 1890 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Scrapbook [Yale-in-China ?], 1903-1913 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Dwight Hall
    - Catalogue of Books, 1886 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Suggestions and "Dope" as to whom Association Record should be sent, 1907-1913 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Subscribers to Dwight Hall, 1882-1891 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Subscribers to Dwight Hall Fund, 1895-1898 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Undergraduate Contributors to Yale Hall Building Fund, 1899 January-June (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Subscribers to the Dwight Hall Fund, 1902 (?) (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Visitor's Register -- Dwight Hall [see YRG 39-A]
  - Writings and Clippings
    - 3 Historical Essays about the Y.M.C.A. and Church of Christ
      - "The Yale Christian Social Union" by E. L. Parsons, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - "Church of Christ in Yale College" by Herbert Parsons, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - "Revivals at Yale" by Max Baird, undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - "Aims and Objectives of Higher Education", 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Clippings scrapbook, 1886-1888 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Clippings, 1889 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Clippings scrapbook
      - 1889-1890 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - 1886-1894 (Box 12)
      - 1894-1905 (Box 13)
      - 1899-1908 (Box 14)
      - 1903-1916 (Box 15)
      - 1908-1911 (Box 16)
      - 1911-1914 (Box 17)
- Records, circa 1911-1980; Accession 1988-A-105
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - Abbe, CC, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ab, 1916-1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ac, 1931-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Achilles, Paul S., 1920-1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ackley, Ernest, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ad, 1914-1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adams, Donald A., 1916-1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adams, H. Sage, 1934-1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adams, John Maxwell, 1939-1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ae - Ak, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Al, 1915-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aldrich, Guy V., 1915-1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Allen, circa Durand, 1914-1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Allen, Devere, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Allen, Waldo M., 1916-1926 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Allenby, Hubert A., 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alter, James P., 1939-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Am, 1916-1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - An, 1913-1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Anderson, K. Brooke, 1926-1945 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Andrews, E.D., 1928-1936 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Andrus, Robert G., 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Angell, James R., 1921-1949 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Anthony, Byron Kenneth, 1927-1944 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ap, 1941-1962 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ar, 1915-1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Arnold, Dorothy, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Arnold, Lauren, 1931-1938 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Arnold, Thomas L., 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - As, 1926-1935 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Ashworth, Katherine, 1926-1928 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Assmann, Frank A., 1916-1944 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - At, 1919-1933 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Au, 1913-1939 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Audette, Lewis G., 1916 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Austin, Judy, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Av, 1926-1928 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Ay, 1935-1939 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Aylsworth, George, 1931-1939 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bab - Ban, 1916-1956 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Babcock, Fern, 1933-1945 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bacon, B.W., 1913-1928 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bader, Jesse M., 1937-1945 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Bailey, James H., 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Bailey (Other), 1916-1962 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Baker, Everett Moore, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Baker, Julia, 1927-1932 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Baker (Other), 1916-1971 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Baldwin, De Witt circa, 1926-1962 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Baldwin, Graham A., 1936-1956 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Baldwin (Other), 1916-1962 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Ballou, Earle H., 1915-1940 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Bar - Baz, 1915-1959 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Barber, B.R., 1916-1939 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Barbour, Katherine H., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Barbour, Marion, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Barker, Joseph E., 1915-1932 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Barnes, Clifford W., 1919-1939 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Barnes, James S., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Barnes, Lincoln W., 1932-1940 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Barnes, William D., 1915-1940 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Barnett, Eugene E., 1937-1945 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Barstow, Robbins W., 1932-1946 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Bartholomew, Marshall, 1926-1945 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Barton, John, 1925-1938 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Bassett, Seymour, 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Batdorf, 1937-1945 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Bates, E.T., 1914-1918 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Bau, M. Joshua, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Baumer, Franklin L., 1932-1944 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Baxley, William H., 1926-1935 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Baxter, John L., 1918, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Bea - Beg, 1913-1944 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Beach, David N., 1914-1946 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Beach, Harlan P., 1916-1927 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Beane, Arthur, 1915-1917 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Beard, William S., 1917 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Beardslee, John W., 1933-1944 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Beardslee (Other), 1917-1955 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Beattie, Philip, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Beh - Bew, 1916-1962 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Bellew, William P., 1926-1932 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Benner, L.circa (Pittsburgh YMCA), 1921 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Bennett, John circa, 1928-1937 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Bennett, R.H., 1918, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Bennett (Other), 1918-1945 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Berger, D. Spencer, 1926-1944 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Berger, Rev. E., 1932-1934 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bernhardt, Louis J., 1917-1930 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Berry, G.T., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Bertsch, William (and Co.), 1913-1919 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Bevis, Palmer, 1925-1941 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Bgate, Arthur, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Bi, 1914-1944 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Biehle, Martha H., 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Biglow, L.H., 1913-1921 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Bilheimer, Robert, 1935-1938 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Bilheimer, Robert S.
    - 1938 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1939 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - 1939 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 1939-1946 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - no date (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Bingham, Brewster, 1931-1944 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Bingham, Hiram, 1926-1944 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Bird, Philip (Utica Presbyterian Church), 1921 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Birge, John Kingsley, 1916-1938 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Birge, Robert B., 1935-1944 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Birge, Robert B., undated (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Bj, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Bl, 1916-1959 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Black, Hugh, 1916-1920 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Blair, Robert F., 1916-1939 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Blakeslee, Clarence W., 1925-1944 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Blanchard, Leslie, 1925-1933 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Blank, Margaret H., 1925-1928 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Bliss, Charles F., 1934-1945 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Bliss, John, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Boa - Bog, 1919-1944 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Bollinger, Heil D., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Bolt - Bon, 1915-1926 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Bone, Harry, 1925-1939 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Bonn - Borc, 1916-1946 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Borden, Mary W., 1916-1918 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Borden, Mrs. William, 1915-1926 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Bord - Bow, 1914-1956 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Borrowes, John, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Bowers, Raymond R., 1938 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Bowers - Boy, 1915-1963 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Boyles, Rev. John, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Boyles, Rev. John, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Boyles, Rev. John, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Boyles, John: personal, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 132 - 133)
  - Bra, 1915-1978? (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Bradford, Arthur H., 1915-1944 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Bradley, Al, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Bradley, Sally, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Bradley (Other), 1914-1961 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Braisted, Paul J., 1935-1946 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Braisted, William E., 1926-1928 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Bre, 1915-1973 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Bree, Elizabeth, 1928-1931 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Brewster, circaB., 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Brewster, William, 1927-1946 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Brewster (Other), 1915-1939 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Bri, 1914-1974 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Bristol, Lucia T., 1927-1932 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Bro, 1916-1954 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Broeksmit, John S., 1917 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Bromley, C. B., 1932-1939 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Bronson, Clarence W., 1915-1933 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Bronson, Francis W., 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Brookes, George, 1930-1936 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Brooks, Henry S. (Yale Alumni Fund), 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Brown, circa Victor, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Brown, Charles R., 1914-1929 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Brown, Forrest D., 1927-1940 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Brown, Frank L., 1917 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Brown, John Crosby, 1914-1945 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Brown, Merrill E., 1915-1916 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Brown, Samuel A., 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Brown, Thatcher M., 1917-1955 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Brown, Walter T., 1930-1940 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Brown, William Adams, 1926-1939 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Brown (Other), 1915-1956 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Browne:
    - Eleanor K., 1915-1943 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - M.B.
    - Thomas M.
  - Bru, 1926-1946 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Bruen, Harriettes, 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Bry, 1916-1962 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Buchanan, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Buchman, Frank no date, 1915-1921 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Buck, Norman S., 1938-1955 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Buck - Buckner, 1913-1956 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Bue - Bul, 1913-1946 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Buehler, H.G., 1915-1919 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Bunch, F.M., 1921 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Bunch, Pardue, 1935-1938 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Bundy, Harvey H., 1917 (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Bundy, McGeorge, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Bundy, W - Bunn, 1916-1939 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Burd - Burn, 1914-1945 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Burnham, Rufus B., 1916-1918 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Burns, Samuel (National War Work Council), 1918 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Burr, Beatrice, 1931-1933 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Burr, B - Burw, 1916-1974 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Bus - Butc, 1915-1944 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Butler, Charles E., 1925-1940 (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Butler, E - Butte, 1916-1956 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Buttrick, George A., 1935-1940 (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Butts, 1913-1916 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Byers, Rev. David M.
  - Student Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 191)
    - 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 192)
    - 1960 (Box 6, Folder 193)
    - 1960 (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - 1960 (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 196 - 197)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 198)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 199)
    - 1963 (Box 6, Folder 200)
    - 1964 (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 202)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 203)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Byers, Harry, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Byron, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - C: unidentified, 1932-1946 (Box 7, Folder 207)
  - Cad - Cal, 1921-1944 (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - Cadigan, Charles, 1925-1945 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Cadigan, George, 1933-1940 (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - Caldwell, 1934-1938 (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - Caldwell, Robert J., 1934-1938 (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - Calhoun, Charles K., 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - Calhoun, Frank, 1918-1941 (Box 7, Folder 214)
  - Calhoun, Robert L., 1926-1941 (Box 7, Folder 215)
  - Calwell, Mary, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 216)
  - Cam - Camp, 1920-1925 (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - Campbell, A.B., 1918 (Box 7, Folder 218)
  - Campbell, A. Verne, 1925-1941 (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - Campbell, Charles S. Correspondence
    - B, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - D, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 221)
    - G, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 222)
    - H, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 223)
    - J, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 224)
    - K, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 225)
    - L, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 226)
    - M, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 227)
    - P - R, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 228)
    - S, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - T, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - W, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - unidentified, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - 1916 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - A, 1916-1917 (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - B, 1916-1917 (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - 1917 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - 1917 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - 1917 (Box 8, Folder 238)
    - C, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 239)
    - D, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 240)
    - E, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 241)
    - F, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 242)
    - G, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 243)
    - H, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 244)
    - H - I, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 245)
    - I, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 246)
    - J, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 247)
    - J - K, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 248)
    - K, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 249)
    - M, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 250)
    - N, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 251)
    - P, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 252)
    - R, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 253)
    - R - S, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 254)
    - S, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 255)
    - S - V, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 256)
    - W, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 257)
    - Y - Z, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 258)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 259)
    - A, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 260)
    - A, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - B, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 262)
    - B, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 263)
    - C, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 264)
    - D - E, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 265)
    - F, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 266)
    - G, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 267)
    - H, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 268)
    - H - K, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 269)
    - L, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 270)
    - M, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 271)
    - R, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 272)
    - S, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 273)
    - W, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 274)
    - 1918 (Box 8, Folder 275)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 9, Folder 276)
    - 1921 (Box 9, Folder 277)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 9, Folder 278)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 9, Folder 279)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 280)
    - 1936 (Box 9, Folder 281)
    - 1937 (Box 9, Folder 282)
    - 1938 (Box 9, Folder 283)
    - 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 284)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 285)
    - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 286)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 287)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 288)
    - Personal
      - 1916 (Box 9, Folder 289)
      - 1916-1919 (Box 9, Folder 290)
      - 1938 (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Campbell, Clair, 1933-1939 (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Campbell, E. Fay
    - Letters from Geneva, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 293)
    - 1917-1937 (Box 9, Folder 294)
    - 1938-1944 (Box 10, Folder 295)
    - 1945-1962 (Box 10, Folder 296)
    - Personal
    - 1917-1921 (Box 10, Folder 297)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 10, Folder 298)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 299)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 300)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 301)
    - 1933 (Box 10, Folder 302)
    - 1934 (Box 10, Folder 303)
    - 1935 (Box 10, Folder 304)
    - 1936 (Box 10, Folder 305)
    - 1937 (Box 10, Folder 306)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 307)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 308)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 309)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 310)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 311)
    - 1939, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 312)
    - 1943-1946 (Box 11, Folder 313)
    - no date (Box 11, Folder 314)
  - no date (Box 11, Folder 315)
  - Campbell, Frank, 1927-1941 (Box 11, Folder 316)
  - Campbell, Fred, 1928-1941 (Box 11, Folder 317)
  - Campbell, G. S., 1919-1941 (Box 11, Folder 318)
  - Campbell, James R., 1915-1917 (Box 11, Folder 319)
  - Campbell, James W., 1925-1941 (Box 11, Folder 320)
  - Campbell, William P., 1915-1945 (Box 11, Folder 321)
  - Campbell (Other), 1915-1956 (Box 11, Folder 322)
  - Can, 1915-1939 (Box 11, Folder 323)
  - Cannon, H.B. Jr., 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 324)
  - Cap, 1920-1936 (Box 11, Folder 325)
  - Capen, Samuel, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 326)
  - Carlisle - Carlton, 1916-1946 (Box 11, Folder 327)
  - Carnevale - Carney, 1915-1927 (Box 11, Folder 328)
  - Carpenter, 1927-1946 (Box 11, Folder 329)
  - Carpenter, Ernest circa, 1920-1933 (Box 11, Folder 330)
  - Carpenter, Sylvia, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 331)
  - Carroll, Douglas, 1935-1941 (Box 12, Folder 332)
  - Carroll, Harriet, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 333)
  - Carroll, Richard circa, 1935-1945 (Box 12, Folder 334)
  - Carr - Carruthers, 1914-1919 (Box 12, Folder 335)
  - Carruthers, Donald W., 1920-1938 (Box 12, Folder 336)
  - Carson, Ralph W., 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 337)
  - Carter - Cartwright, 1916-1939 (Box 12, Folder 338)
  - Carver - Cary, 1919-1939 (Box 12, Folder 339)
  - Cas, 1914-1933 (Box 12, Folder 340)
  - Case, Adelaide, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 341)
  - Cate, Philip, 1925-1927 (Box 12, Folder 342)
  - Cat - Cav, 1932-1956 (Box 12, Folder 343)
  - Cha, 1914-1981 (Box 12, Folder 344)
  - Chalmers, Allen K., 1927-1939 (Box 12, Folder 345)
  - Chalmers, A. Burns (Rev.), 1926-1944 (Box 12, Folder 346)
  - Chalmers, Rebecca, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 347)
  - Chalmers (Other), 1915-1926 (Box 12, Folder 348)
  - Chance, Harold, 1935-1940 (Box 12, Folder 349)
  - Chandler, Robert L., 1938-1944 (Box 12, Folder 350)
  - Chandler, Tracy circa, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 351)
  - Chaplin, Maxwell, 1913-1919 (Box 12, Folder 352)
  - Che, 1915-1970 (Box 12, Folder 353)
  - Cheek, Mary Ashby, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 354)
  - Chen, Francis H.circa, 1936-1939 (Box 12, Folder 355)
  - Cheney, Ralph L., 1925-1936 (Box 12, Folder 356)
  - Cheney (Other), 1939-1956 (Box 12, Folder 357)
  - Cherrington, B.M., 1921-1928 (Box 12, Folder 358)
  - Chester, Nelson B. (Rev.), 1917 (Box 12, Folder 359)
  - Chi, 1915-1974 (Box 12, Folder 360)
  - Chin, Rockwood, 1935-1944 (Box 12, Folder 361)
  - Chin, Nesley, 1938-1946 (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - Chism, Murray S., 1916-1917 (Box 12, Folder 363)
  - Chism, Murray S., 1917-1926 (Box 12, Folder 364)
  - Cho - Chr, 1916-1946 (Box 13, Folder 365)
  - Christman, Earl, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 366)
  - Chu, 1933-1945 (Box 13, Folder 367)
  - Cla - Clay, 1919-1973 (Box 13, Folder 368)
  - Clark, Alden H., 1919-1941 (Box 13, Folder 369)
  - Clark, Annette, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 370)
  - Clark, Arthur B., 1926-1934 (Box 13, Folder 371)
  - Clark, Arthur B. Jr., 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 372)
  - Clark, Arthur B. Jr., 1936-1937 (Box 13, Folder 373)
  - Clark, Arthur B. Jr., 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 374)
  - Clark, Arthur B., 1938-1962 (Box 13, Folder 375)
  - Clark, Byron N., 1915-1927 (Box 13, Folder 376)
  - Clark, circaB. - Clark, circaJ., 1917-1940 (Box 13, Folder 377)
  - Clark, Ch - Clark, El, 1915-1982 (Box 13, Folder 378)
  - Clark, Ernest H., 1915-1925 (Box 13, Folder 379)
  - Clark, Fr - Clark, He, 1917-1956 (Box 13, Folder 380)
  - Clark, J.circa, 1928-1935 (Box 13, Folder 381)
  - Clark, J.T. - Clarke, 1915-1959 (Box 13, Folder 382)
  - Cleaveland, Livingston W., 1915-1926 (Box 13, Folder 383)
  - Cleaver - Clemont D., 1925-1959 (Box 13, Folder 384)
  - Clemont, Norman P., 1926-1946 (Box 13, Folder 385)
  - Clement, Stuart H., 1914-1957 (Box 13, Folder 386)
  - Clemont, Stephen Merrell, 1915-1939 (Box 13, Folder 387)
  - Clen - Clif, 1916-1956 (Box 13, Folder 388)
  - Clinchey, Russell, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 389)
  - Clinchy, Everitt, 1925-1939 (Box 13, Folder 390)
  - Clis - Clo, 1915-1960 (Box 13, Folder 391)
  - Cly, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 392)
  - Cobble, Robin R., 1930 (Box 13, Folder 393)
  - Cobur - Cochran S., 1930-1965 (Box 13, Folder 394)
  - Cochran, William F., 1916-1945 (Box 13, Folder 395)
  - Cock - Cod, 1936-1939 (Box 13, Folder 396)